{
    "id": "d173c9a069054253b890caf1cc958c91",
    "title": "Non-finites exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ba9f08f33c8e4101ac0fbf5a9185ee8d",
            "title": "Non-finites Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "............................ his lesson, he went out  to play cricket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Learnt",
                        "Learning",
                        "Having learnt"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................... along the street one day, I saw a dead cobra.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Walked",
                        "Walking",
                        "Having walked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................... the forest we advanced into the open plain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Leaving",
                        "Left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................ out of his country, he sought asylum in a foreign land.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Driving",
                        "Driven",
                        "Having driven"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ........................... a very hot day, I remained in my tent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "being",
                        "been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A gipsy, ........................ across the meadows, found the child.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wandering",
                        "wandered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I once saw a man .......................... on a rope.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "walking",
                        "walked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not ........................ my way, I asked a policeman.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knowing",
                        "known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................ the noise, I woke up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hearing",
                        "Heard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................ paralytic, he could not walk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Being",
                        "Having been",
                        "Been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}